His story began when it all ended.
The I Inside is a thriller, mystery, drama film directed by Roland Suso Richter.
When Simon awakens in the hospital after surviving a near-fatal accident,
amnesia has erased the last two years from his memory.
He learns that his brother was killed, he has married a woman he doesn't
remember and he's haunted by strange visions of the woman he loved.
Simon Cable, played by Ryan Phillippe.
Clair, played by Sarah Polley.
Anna, played by Piper Perabo.
Peter, played by Robert Sean Leonard.
Doctor Newman, played by Stephen Rea.
Nurse Clayton, played by Rakie Ayola.
The I Inside is a 2004 psychological thriller directed by Roland Suso Richter.
It was written by Michael Cooney based on his own play Point of Death.
This film has no connection with the science-fiction
novel The I Inside, by Alan Dean Foster.
The film explores themes of infidelity, amnesia, nightmare, paranoia, time.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.